George List papers, 1894-2008 C424
Indiana University Archives
- Research, 1894; 1953-2006; undated (Box 9)
  - Ongoing Research, 1984 (Box 9)
  - Research & Graduate Development, 1981-1995 (Box 9)
  - Tayler Album and Field Notes, 1960-1961 (Box 9)
  - Thai and Cambodian Catalog, 1966; 1991 (Box 9)
  - Thai Project, 1959-1960 (Box 9)
  - Turkish Catalog, 1992 (Box 9)
  - The Wake: Cross-Cultural Notes, undated (Box 9)
  - Hopi Slips, 1950s (Box 9)
  - Groupí Zapata, 1964-1989 (Box 10)
    (14 slides removed)
  - Copy of Final Puwva Score (1986?), undated (Box 10)
  - "Stability and Variation in a Hopi Lullaby" Illustrations, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Article - 2 Flutes and a Rattle, Recordings Used, undated (Box 10)
  - Essays in Ethno: Cambridge U Press, undated (Box 10)
  - Completed but not Published,Fauré Article, undated (Box 10)
  - Completed but no Broadcast or Issued (Box 10)
    - Radio WFIU (post 1977), undated (Box 10)
    - Radio Spots, undated (Box 10)
    - Radio Series Folk Song and Social Change. Prospectus and Program Ideas. Also Composed Theme., 1956 (Box 10)
    - The Play Party. Radio Pilot for NAEB "Folk Song and Social Change", 1956 (Box 10)
    - Radio Program, Music of South America. For Latin American Series of Orrego- Salas at IU, undated (Box 10)
  - In-Progress Books - Folksong in Western Civilization, 1968 (Box 10)
  - In-Progress Articles (Box 10)
    - Article: Ethnomusicology: Scope and Problems, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Article: The Subdominant Chord, Theory and Practice", undated (Box 10)
  - In-Progress Audio-Visual (Box 10)
    - Bailes Costeños Album Notes Ver. 1 w/ Marc Satter-White, 1990-1991 (Box 10)
      (5 photographs and negatives removed)
    - Atlantic Coast Region Map, undated (Box 10)
    - Colombian Album Texts, Some Translations, undated (Box 10)
    - Previous Costeños Articles, 1968 (Box 10)
    - Folksongs of America's History: The Westward Movement (1787-1853), instructional video, 1966 (Box 10)
  - Materials for Articles and Lectures (Box 10)
    - Articles/Columbia (incl. by Delia Zapata), 1964 (Box 10)
    - Colombia, Indians, Misc., undated (Box 10)
  - Cofan and Lowland Quichua Studies (Box 10)
    - Ecuador, Indians, Notes, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Ecuador Contents of recordings L77-94, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Ecuador, Indians, Misc., undated (Box 10)
    - Notes on Harp, Ecuador, Maiguschca, 1965 (Box 10)
  - Colombia, Atlantic Coast, Miscellaneous (Box 10)
    - Colombia, Atlantic Coast. List of Slides and Film, 1964-1965; 1968 (Box 10)
    - Col. 70, List of slides and photos, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Colombia, Indians, Misc., undated (Box 10)
    - Evitar, Genealogy, Summer, 1968 (Box 10)
    - Notes on Velorio, Pilar y Victoria Martínez, Cartagena, March 6, 1965 (Box 10)
    - F 816, Velorio in Evitar, undated (Box 10)
    - Velorio – Radio, undated (Box 10)
  - Colombia, Atlantic Coast, Texts (Box 10)
    - Tran. Col. To San Jacinto, Cartagena, List Col 21, 2nd part, 28, 1964; 1968 (Box 10)
    - Evitar, Text Transcriptions by Fraboschi, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Evitar, New Maps: Visuals, undated (Box 10)
      (6 slides and negatives removed)
    - Columbia Text Transcriptions, undated (Box 10)
    - Atlantic Coast – Informants, 1965 (Box 10)
  - Colombia, Pacific Coast (Box 10)
    - Colombia – Pacific Coast. Buenaventura, Notes, September 1964 (Box 10)
    - Colombia – Pacific Coast, Instructions on Assembly Marimba in University Mus., undated (Box 10)
  - Colombia, Questionnaire (Box 10)
    - Colombia, Atlantic Coast, Questionnaire, 1964-1965 (Box 10)
  - Ecuador (Box 10)
    - Ecuador Panpipes, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Indians, South America, Missionary Pamphlet, 1960s (Box 10)
    - Walker, Dorothy, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 10)
    - 93 Peller, David, "The Victory Ceremony of the Jibaro Indians," F 495, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
    - Jívaro, Catalogue of Records, Peller Contract, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Jívaro, Notes on Recordings, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Jívaro, Towsend, Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 10)
    - Jívaro Texts, 1966 (Box 10)
    - Perú, Aguaruna. Documentation of recordings by Gerhard Fast., undated (Box 10)
    - Jívaro Anenter, 1971 (Box 10)
  - Ecuador Studies (Box 10)
    - Ecuador, list of publications lent to me by Maiguaschca., undated (Box 10)
    - Catalogue: List Field 148-151 (List Ecuador 77-82) Izamba and Pillero folk harp., 1965 (Box 10)
  - Hopi 1960 Studies (Box 10)
    - Hopi Tape Transcriptions, 1960 (Box 10)
    - List of Hopi Songs, Excerpts Sent to Chief, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Hopi Notes, Summer, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Hopi Notes, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Hopi Symbolism, 1957; 1960 (Box 10)
    - Hopi – Informants, Copy, Correspondence With, 1960-1965 (Box 10)
    - Hopi Questionnaire, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Hopi Tapes 1-10 Transcriptions, 1960 (Box 10)
  - Hopi Studies, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Hopi 63, List of Recordings, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Hopi 63, Interview with Stella Adams, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Hopi 63, Translations, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Hopi 63, Information Abstracted from Tapes, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Hopi 63, Information, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Hopi 63, Description of Dances, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Hopi 63, Correspondence, Abbott Sekequaptewa, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Hopi Photos, 1963 (Box 10)
      (41 photographs and negatives removed)
  - Velorio (Box 10)
    - General, 1954 (Box 10)
    - Venezuela, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Notes - Pilar y Victoria Martínez, Cartagena, March 6, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Article by Lenz, 1953 (Box 10)
    - Article from Murcia, (photocopy), 1894 (Box 10)
    - Article "Blanco y Negro", 1970 (Box 10)
      (3 photographs and negatives removed)
    - Notes from Spain, undated (Box 10)
  - Veloria, Non-Colombia (Box 10)
    - Chapter on Velatorio and Article on Velatorio from Blanco y Negro, undated (Box 10)
    - López Cruz, Francisco, La Música Folklórico de Puerto Rico, excerpt, Volario, 1967 (Box 10)
  - List-5 Inserts 1st Program, "Folk Music" from TV "Folk Music of the World", 1956 (Box 11)
  - List-5 Inserts 1st Program, "Folk Music" from TV "Folk Music of the World", 1956 (Box 11)
  - List 6 Series Theme for "Music in the Life of Man" Played on Bassoon by Roy Houser, 1957 (Box 11)
  - List-10 Various Recordings of "Lady Isabel and the Elf Knight, undated (Box 11)
  - List 21-23 Additional Recordings Prepared for but not used in Hopi Pilot Film, undated (Box 11)
  - List-27, Play Party Songs, Sung by Alice and Larry Sherman, 1956 (Box 11)
  - List 28-29 Demonstration Tapes of Materials for use in "Music and Infancy", undated (Box 11)
  - List-31 Children's Songs from French Pyrennes Sung by Eve, Hans Wolf, Valdettaro & Naylor, undated (Box 11)
  - List-32 Yiddish Children's Songs and Love Songs, Sung by Ruth Rubin, 1958 (Box 11)
  - List-35 Copy of Sound Track of Takes of Lullabies, TV, "Music in Infancy", 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-37, "Golden Slumbers" Soundbook, undated (Box 11)
  - List-39, "Caroling on the Carillon" Columbia LP, 17 carols, undated (Box 11)
  - List-43, Young People in Indiana in Generations Past, undated (Box 11)
  - List-44Copy of Demonstration Tape Made for the Sayres, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-52 and 53, Illustrations, Lecture on American Folk Music, Women's Faculty Club, 1957 (Box 11)
  - List-54, Various Versions of "Fair Charlotte" from the Archives, undated (Box 11)
  - List-55, Diverse Jewish Music Recordings, University of Jerusalem, Institute of Oriental Music, undated (Box 11)
  - List-57, Versions of Gypsy Davy from Archives, 1954-1955 (Box 11)
  - List-60, Copy of "Jewish Children's Songs and Games," Folkways Album Sung by Ruth Rubin, 1957 (Box 11)
  - List-61, Copy of Items Collected from Children in Bloomington by List See Original List-59, 1955 (Box 11)
  - Music-62, 63, Children's Songs from Halpert's Collections, undated (Box 11)
  - List-64, Miscellaneous Children's Songs Dubbed for Possible use in TV Film "Music and Childhood", undated (Box 11)
  - List-65, Midterm and Final Exams, Music U301-302, 1958-1959 (Box 11)
  - List-66, Practice Tape for Music U 301, Made Fall, 1958 (Box 11)
  - List-67, Classroom Dictation Material for Music U301-302, Used, 1958-1959 (Box 11)
  - List-71, Materials Selected for Possible use in Persian Art Film, 1958 (Box 11)
  - List-76, F480, Demonstration Tape, Forms and Texture, undated (Box 11)
  - List-76, Demonstration Tape for Music U 301-302, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-77, Transcription Materials (For Elementary Class, 59-60), 1966 (Box 11)
  - List-78, Outside Dictation, 1959-1960 (Box 11)
  - List-79, Dictation (advanced), 1959-1960 (Box 11)
  - List-84, Demo Tape for Talk, Holbrook Rotary Club & Keams Canyon Lion's Club, Understanding the Music of Other Peoples, Summer, 1960 (Box 11)
  - List-85, 86, Japanese Music, Units I & II, undated (Box 11)
  - List-87, "Folk Song of the Allegheny Mountains," Example of Cultivated Style Sung by F. Gainer, 1958 (Box 11)
  - List-88 3 Black, Robert, "Chinese Songs Collected at IU & Transcribed," Music U 302, Recordings, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-92, "Carols of All Nations," Jean Ritchie with Harpsichord and Recorder, Tradition Records, undated (Box 11)
  - List-93, Exams, Music U301-302, 1959-1960 (Box 11)
  - List-94, Lee and List Conversation Concerning Lee's Tapes Copied for the Archives, undated (Box 11)
  - List-104-105, Demo Tapes for "Folk Music in Western Civilization", undated (Box 11)
  - List-106, Exams, Music U 301-302, 1960-1961 (Box 11)
  - List-114, Norwegian Version of "Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star", 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-121, Test of Sarkes Tarzian Recording Tape, undated (Box 11)
  - List-122, Materials for Persian Art Film, "The Seven Wives of Bahram Gur", 1960 (Box 11)
  - List-129, Demo Tape for Talk on Development of Sound Track for Persian Art Film, 1961 (Box 11)
  - List-130, Demonstration Tape to Accompany Transcriptions of Aurally Transmitted Music, undated (Box 11)
  - List-136, 137, Hopi Demonstration Tape, Tape Session, Sem. (George List), Dec. 1960 (Box 11)
  - List-138, Class Transcription, Persian Flute & Gold Coast Song at Various Speeds and Filterings, undated (Box 11)
  - List-144-149, Copies of Demonstration Tapes Sent to William Abbott, June 1961 (Box 11)
  - List-150, Demonstration Tape Used for SEM and Ethnolinguistic Seminar Lectures on Thai Speech and Song, undated (Box 11)
  - List-152, Thai Songs and Conversation by Kanda Thammongkol and Sakon Changsanit, made, Dec. 2, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-153, Original Tape for Thai Analysis, Song, Speech, & Announcements. Kanda, Sakon, and Swat, undated (Box 11)
  - List-154, Thai Materials Organized for Analysis. Eleven Items, Song, then Speech by Two or More Speakers, undated (Box 11)
  - List-155, Thai Materials for Analysis, Song and Spoken Texts. Sakon, Kanda, Suhong, Vayawananda, Kay Attagara, undated (Box 11)
  - List-156-192, Copies of BBC Transcription Discs, List of Song Titles in English Language, 1957 (Box 11)
  - List-156, 157, Memories of a Ballad Hunter. Lomax. BBC I. America - The Ballad Singers - Pts. 1 & 2, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-158, 159, Memories of a Ballad Hunter. Lomax. BBC II. America - Harmony and Hillbilly Parts 1 & 2, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-160, 161, Memories of a Ballad Hunter. Lomax. BBC III. Spain - From Seville to the Pyrennes Pts. 1 & 2, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-162, 163, Memories of a Ballad Hunter. Lomax. BBC IV. Spain. From Vigo to San Sebastian, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-164, 165, Memories of a Ballad Hunter. Lomax. BBC V. Italy - Sicily and Calabria Pts. 1 & 2, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-166, 167, Memories of a Ballad Hunter. Lomax. BBC VI. Italy - Puglia to Genoa Parts 1 & 2, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-168, A Ballad Hunter Looks at Britain. Lomax. BBC I. Come Listen to My Song, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-169, A Ballad Hunter Looks at Britain. Lomax. BBC II. From Devon to Dover, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-170, A Ballad Hunter Looks at Britain. Lomax. BBC III. From Cornwall to Yorkshire, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-171, A Ballad Hunter Looks at Britain. Lomax. BBC IV. East Anglia to the Border, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-172, A Ballad Hunter Looks at Britain. Lomax. BBC V. Folksongs of the Lowlands, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-173, A Ballad Hunter Looks at Britain. Lomax. BBC VI. Songs of the Highlands & Islands, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-174, A Ballad Hunter Looks at Britain. Lomax. BBC VII. From Dublin to Donegal, Ireland, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-175, A Ballad Hunter Looks at Britain. Lomax. BBC VIII. Songs from the North & South, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-176, British Folk Songs. Lomax. BBC transcrip. 1. Collecting in the Past, Maud Karpeles, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-177, British Folk Songs. Lomax. BBC transcrip., 2. Collecting Today on Disc and Tape, Brian George, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-178, British Folk Songs. Lomax. BBC transcrip., 3. Regional Variants, Peter Kennedy, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-179, British Folk Songs. Lomax. BBC transcrip., 4. American Relations, Seamus Ennis, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-180, British Folk Songs. Lomax. BBC transcrip., 5. Accompaniments, Patrick Shuldham-Shaw, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-181, British Folk Songs. Lomas. BBC transcrip., 6. Folksongs Today, A.L. Lloyd, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-182, The Grammaphone Today. BBC transcription, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-183, 184, Folk Songs of Rumania. Parts 1 & 2. BBC. A. L. Lloyd, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-185, Ballads and Blues. BBC. Peter Kennedy, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-186, Make Mine Country, (A Musical Tour of the British Isles), 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-187-188, Folk Songs of Texas, Alan Lomax. BBC transcriptions, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-189, Argentine Folk Songs. BBC, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-190, Folksongs from Chile. BBC, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-191, 192, Cante Jondo, Parts 1 and 2. BBC, 1959 (Box 11)
  - List-196, Examinations Music U 301-302, 1961-62 (Box 11)
  - List-201, "The Boundaries of Speech and Song," November 17, 1961 (Box 11)
  - List-210-211, Materials, Copy of Contents of Demonstration Tapes 210-211, undated (Box 11)
  - List-212-213, (Duplicates) Demonstration of Means of Notating Materials Lying Between Speech and Song, undated (Box 11)
  - List-235, Demonstration Tape for "The Folk Music of the Atlantic Coast of Colombia, Intro.," IU, 26 Apr. 1965 (Box 11)
  - List-245, Demonstration Tape for "Ethnomusicology in Higher Education," Watson's College Music Class, 1962 (Box 11)
  - List-286, Inserts for Lecture, "El Estudio de la Música Folklórica", Sept. 15, 1964 (Box 11)
  - List-287, Various Inserts Used and not Used in Lectures in Colombia, 1964-65 (Box 11)
  - List-288, Television, Bogotá, Escobar's Program, September 2, 1964 (Box 11)
  - List-297-301, Hopi Excerpts Tapes 1-2, 1960 (Box 11)
  - List-289, Illustrations of Shape Note Singing for Anthropology 495, 1st Sem., 1961-62 (Box 11)
  - List-316, Materials for "Symbolism in Hopi Song and Chant", 1969 (Box 11)
  - List-317, Hopi Speech, Transcriptions by C.V. Voegelin, 1960 (Box 11)
  - List-319, Jívaro, Mola, 1963 (Box 11)
  - List-320, Instituto Ecuatoriano de Folklore, Lican, etc., 1962 (Box 11)
  - List-321-324, Auca, Ecuador, Peek. Interview with Leeke on the Recordings, 1965 (Box 11)
  - List-339-341, Piano Recital by Eve's Students, May 14, 1961 (Box 11)
  - List-343, Tape Illustrating Paper by R. Taylor, "Traditional Brass Bands in New Orleans, Louisiana," for F489, 1968 (Box 11)
  - List-344-347, Recordings Used for Transcription and Analysis in F386, 1967 (Box 11)
  - List-363, Recordings for Use in F386, 1967 (Box 11)
  - List-376-379, Recordings Accompanying Abraham and Foss, Anglo-American Folksong Style, 1972 (Box 11)
  - List-414, Demo Tape to Accompany Semenarios de Etnomusicología Musica, Mexico City, 16-20 Ag., 1971 (Box 11)
  - List-420, "Material and Non-Material Contributions of the Negro to Colombian Folklore", 1971 (Box 11)
  - List-431, Music of the Khen, Demo Tape with Paper by Attagara, K., "Khen, A Thai Musical Instrument," Paper No. 98, undated (Box 11)
  - List 432-Demo Tape, F392, Folk Music in Western Civilization, undated (Box 11)
  - List 435-Demo Tape, Diffusion and Modification of an Afro-American Clarinet, SEM Meetings, Oct. 25, 1974 (Box 11)
  - List-437-440, Demo Tape for Transcription, F480, 1975 (Box 11)
  - COL. TRANS. 33 List Field 165, 2nd pt. 168, (List Col 68: 103, 2nd pt.-106) Cartagena, Conjunto de Gaitas de Malibu, 14 July 1968 (Box 11)
  - COL. TRANS. 32 List Field 164-165, 1st pt. plus List Field 182 (List Col 70: 102-103, 1st pt. plus List Col 68:XIV) Cartagena, Radió Miramar, Decimeros, 3 July 1968 (Box 11)
  - COL. TRANS.34 List Field 169-170 (List Col 68: 107-108) Cartagena, Eugenio Charris Charris, Decimero, 28 July 1968 (Box 11)
  - COL. TRANS. 35 List Field 171-175 (List Col 68: 109-113) Cartagena, Radio Bahía, Cunjunto dé Caña de Millo de Roque Arrieta, 30 July 1968 (Box 11)
  - COL. TRANS. 36 List Field 176-178 (List Col 68: 114-116) Islas Rosarios, Musical Bow and Conjunto de Gaitas, 2 August 1968 (Box 11)
  - List Field 179-180 first part, (List Col 117-118 first part), Evitar, COL 37, August 3, 1968 (Box 11)
  - COL. TRANS. 37 List Field 179-180, 1st pt. (List Col 68: 117-118, 1st pt.), Evitar, 4, August 1, 1968 (Box 11)
  - COL. TRANS. 38 List Field 180, 2nd pt. 181 (List Col 68: 118, 2nd pt. - 119) Cartagena, Lumbalú by Palenqueras, 16 August 1968 (Box 11)
  - COL. TRANS. 39 List Field 184, tracks 1 and 2 (Atlantic Coast Col 68 Caballero and Diaz 1, tracks 1 and 2), Evitar, 22 September 1968 (Box 11)
  - List Field 184, 185, Caballéro Evitar 2, 1968 (Box 11)
  - COL. TRANS. 40 List Field 185, track 1, 1st pt. (Atlantic Coast Caballero and Diaz 2, track 1, 1st pt.) Mahates, Carángano, 19 October 1968 (Box 11)
  - List Field 184, 185 (Caballero, Evitar 1-2 ), 1968 (Box 11)
  - COL. TRANS. 41 List Field 185, track 1 concl. Track 3, 1st part (Atlantic Coast Col 68 Caballero and Diaz 2, track 2 concl., track 2 1st pt.) Evitar, 20 October 1968 (Box 11)
  - COL. TRANS. 42 List Field 185, track concl. (Atlantic Coast Col 68 Caballero and Diaz 2 track 2 concl.) Cartagena, Fiesta de los Inocentes, 1 November 1968 (Box 11)
  - COL. TRANS. 43 List Field 186-187 (List Col 70: 120-121) Cartagena, Decimero Religiosos Joaquín Barrera of Loríca, Córdoba, 10 February 1970 (Box 11)
  - COL. TRANS. 44 List Field 188-189 (List Col 70: 122-123) Manates, Informants from Evitar, Danza de Negro, Bullerengue, and Fandango, 12 April 1970 (Box 11)
  - Texts - 102-103, undated (Box 11)
  - Texts Extracted from Transcriptions, Col., 1964 (Box 11)
  - DC and PC Texts - One 5" Tape, undated (Box 11)
  - Catalogues Colombia (Box 11)
    - Col Cat Copies, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Atlantic Coast Checklist, 1965 (Box 11)
  - Informants Colombia (Box 11)
    - Informants (List made by Delia Zapata), 1964 (Box 11)
  - Oversize, Texts (Décimas), 1968 (Box 11)
- Professional, 1942-2004; undated (Box 12)
  - General, 1942-1989 (Box 12)
    - Faculty Council Talk, Demonstration, November 7, 1967 (Box 12)
    - Faculty Newsletter, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
    - Faculty Reports, 1963-1980 (Box 12)
    - Folklore Institute, 1942-1976 (Box 12)
    - Indiana Committee for the Humanities, 1988 (Box 12)
    - Inter-American Program in Ethnomusicology, 1971 (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous Teaching Materials, 1978; undated (Box 12)
    - Notation Book (Box 12)
      - Notation Seminar - General Folder, 1961 (Box 12)
        (2 negatives removed)
      - Forms, Notation Seminar, Binkele-Hickerson, 1961 (Box 12)
      - Notation Seminar Numbered Forms Filled Out (1), 1961 (Box 12)
      - Notation Seminar Numbered Forms Filled Out (2), 1961 (Box 12)
      - Notation Seminar Numbered Forms Filled Out (3), 1961 (Box 12)
    - Sabbatical Leave, 1968-1975 (Box 12)
    - Speech/Melody Course, 1987-1989 (Box 12)
    - Teaching Awards, 1971 (Box 12)
    - Texas Folklore Congress, 1958-1959 (Box 12)
    - Units I-V, undated (Box 12)
  - Societies and conferences, 1958-1994 (Box 12)
    - International Council of Traditional Music (ICTM), 1982-1987 (Box 12)
    - International Folk Music Council (IFMC) (Box 12)
      - General, 1961 (Box 12)
      - Ghana Meeting, 1965 (Box 12)
      - U.S. Commission, 1966 (Box 12)
      - 19th Conference, Ostend, 1967 (Box 12)
      - Conference, 1967 (Box 12)
      - Executive Secretary, 1969 (Box 12)
      - Jamaica, 1971 (Box 12)
      - 22nd Conference, San Sebastián, Spain, 1973 (Box 12)
      - Conference, Regensberg, August, 1975 (Box 12)
      - 25th Conference, 1979 (Box 12)
    - International Music Council, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Music Academy Conference Program, 36th Conference, 1962 (Box 12)
    - Society for Ethnomusicology (SEM) (Box 12)
      - Indiana University, April 1960 (Box 12)
      - Trip to Berkeley, 1960 (Box 12)
      - Philadelphia, 1961 (Box 12)
      - Meeting, New Orleans, 1966 (Box 12)
      - New Haven, Nov. 1967 (Box 12)
      - Newsletter, 1968 (Box 12)
      - Annual Meeting, Ann Arbor, 1969 (Box 12)
      - 15th Annual Meeting, Seattle, Oct. 29-Nov. 1, 1970 (Box 12)
      - Meeting, 1971 (Box 12)
      - Toronto, 1972 (Box 12)
      - Meeting, 1973 (Box 12)
      - Officers Past and Present, 1973 (Box 12)
      - Newsletter, 1973 (Box 12)
      - Report to on IU, Courses Offered, etc., 1973 (Box 12)
      - Midwest Chapter, March 2 & 3 1974 (Box 12)
      - Meetings, San Francisco, Oct. 1974 (Box 12)
      - Meetings, Wesleyan, 1975 (Box 12)
      - AFS Meetings, Philadelphia, 1976 (Box 12)
      - St. Louis, 1978 (Box 12)
      - Conference, 1980 (Box 12)
      - Conference, Honolulu, HI, 1981 (Box 12)
      - Program, 1987 (Box 12)
      - Council, 1971-1980 (Box 12)
      - Council, 1986 (Box 12)
      - Midwest Chapter, 1973-1984 (Box 12)
      - 1978-1994 (Box 12)
      - Copy of Folder (#28), 1965-1992 (Box 12)
  - Grants and fellowships, 1952-2004 (Box 13)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS) & American Philosophical Society (APS) Hopi Grant Applications, 1962-1963 (Box 13)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS) (Box 13)
      - Application for Research in Colombia, 1964-65 (Box 13)
      - Grants, 1976 (Box 13)
      - Fellowship (Speech/Song), 1988-89 (Box 13)
      - General, 1992 (Box 13)
    - American Philosophical Society (APS) (Box 13)
      - General, 1959-1965 (Box 13)
      - Hopi, 1987 (Box 13)
      - Grant Report Forms, 1989 (Box 13)
      - Speech/Song, 1990 (Box 13)
      - Grant, 1991 (Box 13)
    - Center for Field Work, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Cuentos Grants, 1991 (Box 13)
    - English Exchange Program, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Faculty Grant, 1971 (Box 13)
    - Fellowship Announcements, 1959-1960 (Box 13)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 13)
      - Fellowship, 1955-1956 (Box 13)
      - IU Folklore Grant, Summer 1965 (Box 13)
      - Grant, 1965-1967 (Box 13)
    - Foreign Area Fellowship Program (Box 13)
      - 1972 (Box 13)
      - 1969-1970 (Box 13)
    - Fulbright Commission Report, 1965; 1975 (Box 13)
    - Grants (Box 13)
      - Federal Agencies, Social, Behavioral, Humanities, 1992 (Box 13)
      - Graduate School Research Committee, 1960-1965 (Box 13)
      - How to Secure, 1968 (Box 13)
    - Guggenheim Foundation (Box 13)
      - Application for Research in Colombia, 1964-65 (Box 13)
      - Speech/Melody, IU Grant, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Indiana Committee for the Humanities (ICH) Grant Letter, Info, and Correspondence, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Indiana University (Box 13)
      - Copy of Grant Proposal, 2004 (Box 13)
      - International Projects and Activities Grant, 1994 (Box 13)
      - Marche O'Malley (small grant program), 1988 (Box 13)
      - Phone Funding Requests, 1989 (Box 13)
      - Retired Grant, 1989-1991 (Box 13)
      - Small Grant Program (IU), 1990 (Box 13)
      - Summer Faculty Grants, 1969 (Box 13)
    - IU Foundation (Box 13)
      - Grants, 1963 (Box 13)
      - Research Reports, 1961-1967 (Box 13)
    - Jerome Foundation, 1976 (Box 13)
    - Latin American Music, 1971-1972 (Box 13)
    - Latin American Studies (Box 13)
      - Grant Application, Summer 1968 (Box 13)
      - Colombia-Spain Financial Report, 1970 (Box 13)